U.S. Department of Labor "Labor Organization Annual Report Forms, LM-2" 5860
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Department of Labor "Labor Organization Annual Report Forms, LM-2"
1976-1991
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Department of Labor
5860
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5722530
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 28, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3008 AV: George H. Hildebrand "The Government's Wage-Price Policy: A Long Range View" Speech Audio-Visual Materials /3046: Leonard P. Adams Papers /3091: W. Duane Evans Additional Papers /4012: Kheel Center Files and Circulation Reserve List /4039: Milton R. Konvitz Papers /4040: George H. Hildebrand Papers /4067: Vernon H. Jensen Longshore Research Files /4121: John Burton Papers /4133: J. Gormly Miller Papers /4139: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4158: John P. Windmuller Additional Papers /4170: J. Gormly Miller Additional Papers /4177: J. Gormly Miller Additional Papers /4177 AV: J. Gormly Miller Audio-visual materials /4212: Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence /4228: J. Gormly Miller Additional Files /4250: Ronald Seeber and Robert S. Smith New York State Workers Compensation Pilot Program for Alternative Dispute Resolution Files /4283: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files 5001: American Association for Labor Legislation Records 5001 PAM: American Association for Labor Legislation Pamphlet File 5012: Saul Wallen Papers 5022: George Pearlman Research Papers 5029m: U.S. Women's Bureau "The Employment and Unemployment of Negro Women" Manuscript 5091: U.S. Fact-Finding Board on the Non-ferrous Metals Industry 5129: Maxwell Copelof Arbitration Briefs, Exhibits, Transcripts and Decisions 5143: Anna Weinstock Schneider Papers 5182: William J. Doble Papers 5186: U.S. Department of Labor Survey of Industrial Relations in the Steel Industry 5206-PR: Local 1199 President Leon Davis Records 5220: U.S. Department of Labor News 5225: ALES Records 5226: National Council On Household Employment Records 5228: Charles Uhlinger Papers 5277: Workers Education Bureau of America Records 5307: Consumers' League of New York City Records 5320: U.S. Department of Labor Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division
United States. Department of Labor.
5722530
- 36.34.3.1 LM-2 reports A-B, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 36.34.3 LM-2s C-D-E, 1978-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- LM-2s F-G, 1976-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- LM-2s H - L, 1978-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- LM-2s M - N - O, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- LM-2s M - N - O, 1977-1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- LM-2 Reports P - R, 1977-1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- LM-2 Forms S and Steelworkers, 1976-1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- LM-2 forms S and Steelworkers, 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- LM-2 forms S and Steelworkers, 1966-1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- LM-2s T, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- LM-2s U - W, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 36.34.3.1 LM-2 Reports (Box 3, Folder 1)
- 36.34.3.1. LM-2 Reports A - B, 1981-1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- 36.34.3.1. LM-2 Reports C - E, 1983-1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- 36.34.3 LM-2s F - G, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- 36.34.3.1 LM-2s H - L, 1976-1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- 36.34.3.1 LM-2s M - N - O, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 36.34.3.1. LM-2s P - R, 1986-1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- 36.34.3.1 LM-2s S, 1984-1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- 36.34.3.1. LM-2s T, 1980-1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 36.34.3.1 LM-2s U - W, 1983-1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)